you know, like I saw Viola Davis was following me the other day and I'm sure she doesn't run
her social media, but, uh, I went on her page and I saw that, um, there, there was a post about like
bravery and under it, I put bravery would be speaking about the genocide in Palestine.
Good for you. See, that's why people are mad at you all the time, Amanda. And you know what? I
have that same energy and that's why I like you and I appreciate it because I'm annoying as hell.
You can't take me anywhere anymore. I'd be fighting people at weddings, but it is what it
is at this point. I'm sorry. Don't bring me to talk about the thing. I'm going to talk about
the thing. It is what it is. Okay. So I, let me tell you, I fantasize because you know, I'm not
obviously, uh, in Hollywood or a celebrity or anything like that. So I fantasize about being
annoying, but also mainstream enough that Kamala Harris tries to bring me in to like pacify me,
right? Like I wish I could be as like loud and irritating to these people as you have managed
to be. So I want to hear all about it. Like, do you feel like she's like, she thought this woman's
going to be a problem because, and also let me not skip past this. You, the other red line,
Palestine is obviously a huge red line in American politics. The other one that is less spoken about
because fewer people have crossed it is expressing a willingness not to vote for the democratic nominee
and to have some litmus test and don't be black and don't be a black woman because we all know
we're supposed to be on that democratic party plantation. So you cross all of these lines and
you were agitating around Palestine in the lead up to 2024. Tell me what happened. How did, how did it
come to pass that you ended up being brought in to meet up with Kamala? Um, I, you know, this life
is fascinating because if you really just follow your gut, not your fear, but if you start, if you
really learn how to follow your gut, you, you're actually bugged out how things just land the way
they land. So I, one night was like, Oh, Kimberly Crenshaw, professor Kimberly Crenshaw is doing,
she used to do this thing called, they might still actually do it called, um, freedom summer school,
I think, or summer, summer. She used to do, but like an online class program type thing. And so, um,
I saw they had a session, like David Johns was on there. We went to Columbia together.
So I was like, Oh, let me just tap in, you know, and be in the audience. So they noticed that I
was in the audience and, uh, then they like asked me to talk. And then they had a woman on there named
Barbara Arnwine and she does a lot of voting rights activism. And so we were talking about
voting rights activism and how ultimately it's not just that Republicans are trying to strip voting
rights. It's that Democrats are not doing enough to stop it, right? That they're trying to speak
to democratic leaders and democratic, um, lobbyists about like, how can we actually like actively
prevent this? And they're kind of laissez-faire about it and not considering it to be an important
enough issue to put their energy towards. So I'm like, damn, I really want to know more about that
because post October 7th is when I was radicalized into just simply completely disassociating from the
Democrats. Right. Because it was like, you can't even the smoke and mirrors is not even smoking
mirrors anymore. It's...